UNITE HERE New Engalnd Joint Board Records 6200/006
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE HERE New Engalnd Joint Board Records
1999-2008
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE HERE
6200/006
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records.
7544324
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 11, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 25, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State); Textile workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State); Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; UNITE HERE (Organization)
7544324
- Agreements and correspondence. (Box 1)
  - Ameripride, 2002-2005 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Aramark, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Churchill Linen Services, 2004-2007 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Crown Linen, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Ma-Va, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Morgan, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Laundry 2004, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Scope and Contents
    1 CD inside "UNITE HERE Laundry Health and Safety Materials"
  - Purity Service Inc., 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Confidential Records, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Local 1999 Election (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - AJ Wright 2001 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Originals AJ, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Bryant Hankins (AJ Wright), 2001 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - A.J. Wright, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - A.J. Wright, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - DeJesus, Roberto, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Tomas Cabrera, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Homegoods Executive Board, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Homegoods, 2001-2005 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Home Goods Distribution Center, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - HomeGoods 2000 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Marshalls 2003 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Eveden, 2005-2008 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Hometex Design, 2005-2008 (Box 1, Folder 24)